

TRẦN THỊ MỸ HUYỀN

Business Analyst

Dob: 26/04/2001

Phone: 0706192450

Email: mhuyen81.it@gmail.com

Address: Thu Duc, Ho Chi Minh

OBJECTIVE

I have a strong desire to express myself and be part of an active work environment where I can learn and contribute to the business. My goal is to become a skilled business analyst, providing customers with excellent products and solving business problems. I aim to use my skills and experience to help company attract more customers and enhance the quality of its products.

EDUCATION

2019 - 2023 HCMC University of Technology and Education

Major: Information Technology

GPA: 8.41/10

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Databases	SQLserver, MySQL, Sharepoint,
Tools	- VS Code, Postman, MS Office

Soft skills Presentation, communication, teamwork, critical thinking, collaboration,...

- Figma, Astah, Adobe XD, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Ps

WORK EXPERIENCE

3/2023 - Now **Vu Thao Technology**Customer Service

11/2022 - 02/2023 New Star Paper manufacturing trade co., ltd

Business Analyst

02/2022 - 10/2022 New Star Paper manufacturing trade co., ltd

Front-end developer

- Project development: Apply HTML/CSS, Javascript, ReactJS to frontent
- Work with BA and testers to perfect the software to suit user needs

9/2021 - 6/2022 HCMC University of Technology and Education

Teaching Assistant for Databases

- Support teachers to prepare lessons for class
- Support the teacher to mark the exam and answer students' questions

PROJECTS

Edocman MSB

(2023 - 2024)

Customer	Maritime Bank
Description	The website applies the Sharepoint platform to eOffice with many functions such as: Digitally signing and releasing documents, text libraries, news, discussions,
Team size	> 10
Your position in project	Customer Service
Your responsibility project	- Discuss, analyze and clarify customer requirements - Training and implementing software operating instructions - Writing documents: FSD, User manual, Test case, Coordinate with programmers to handle errors, test and solve problems
Technologies	Sharepoint, SQLserver, Postman, Figma,

Website

(2023 - 2024)

Customer	EVNGENCO3
Description	- Apply Sharepoint platform to EVNGENCO3's admin website for functional management and authorization - Build a basic website for a public site
Team size	> 10
Your position in project	Customer Service // Tester
Your responsibility project	- Writing documents: FSD, User manual, Test case, Coordinate with programmers to handle errors, test and solve problems
Technologies	Sharepoint, QLserver,

ERP - Website eCommerce

(2022 - 2023)

Customer	New Star Paper manufacturing trade co., ltd
Description	- ERP website for industrial business - eCommerce website for retail business
Team size	10
Your position in project	Business Analyst
Your responsibility project	- Perform system analysis and operational process design - Update the system, provide solutions and development directions - Write document, test application,
Technologies	SQLserver, Figma, Adobe XD, MISA

HONORS & AWARDS

01/2024	Award for Student of 5 merits at the School level 3 years 2020-2023
2019 - 2023	Nguyen Truong To Scholarship for 4 years 2019-2023
2019 - 2020	POWER ON Scholarship of Student Assistance Center HCM 2019-2020

CERTIFICATIONS	
01/2023	TOEIC 540 certificate
9/2021	Teaching Assistant Certificate
ACTIVITIES	
6/2021 - 12/2022	Faculty of Information Technology - HCMC University of Technology and Education
	Head of MFIT - Media Faculty of Information Technology
	 In charge of managing human resources and products of the team Participate in organizing programs and academic competitions at faculty level: Hackathon, Mastering IT, BeCoder,
	 Promote programs and activities of the Faculty through media publications
9/2019 - 6/2021	Faculty of Information Technology - HCMC University of Technology and Education
	Collaborators
	Participate in social work activities
	 Participate in supporting and organizing programs of the Union - Faculty of Information
	Technology Association © topcv.vn